hi there over the last 21 years we have
written sales copy that has done over a
$1 million in sales and the one thing
that I have learned is that if you can
write sales copy effectively you will
never struggle to get sales in your
business my name is Jer M Kowski and
I've spent my entire career working with
coaches mentors trainers people that
create courses back then we did CD and
DVD products and everything boils down
to the sales copy the written words that
get people to take action when they see
a page on the internet anytime you visit
a page on the internet there are words
that speak to the mind of the prospect
as to what they are buying into and if
you can learn how to effectively write
sales copy the right way you will never
wonder where your next sale is going to
come from okay and so again just a
little bit about me I've been doing this
for a long time I built multiple
businesses mentored thousands of people
on how to create six and seven figure
success and my businesses have done
over10 to $20 million per year in profit
in this space and Industry and so I want
to break down for you what those best
strategies are that actually work that
you can do that you can take from this
video that are repeatable that are
duplicatable and here's the thing I'm
going to be teaching you stuff that you
will not here anywhere else promise you
that I will be showing you some
techniques that may go go against what
you think are normal but can I tell you
this that by the end of this video if
you follow along if you stay engaged you
will have the blueprint to writing eight
and nine figure sales copy for you I'm
going to show you when to use artificial
intelligence which honestly I would not
recommend you do or rely on and I'm
going to tell you why that is I'm also
going to show you the right way and the
wrong way way to write sales copy that
actually works okay one thing I want to
say you might have seen in the thumbnail
I had this book The Ultimate Sales
letter by Dan Kennedy and Dan Kennedy is
a legend in the online marketing space
magnetic marketing his nobs inner circle
you can see right here here's Dan
talking speaking right over here he
carries an incredible energy about him
when he speaks and teaches but he has
written hundreds of millions of dollars
in sales copy and I would highly
recommend plugging into any of his
content his books on YouTube he's kind
of like the grandfather the old
grandfather you know of this industry
and his methods still work and they are
not on trial to this day even why
advertising fails this book that I have
here in my hand The Ultimate Sales
letter it's worth the read this alone
has hundreds of millions of dollars in
sales copyrighting tactics and
techniques and I borrow from more often
than not anything the very first chapter
of what he calls the Kennedy system in
this book and what I help people do what
I have done though is I have established
and built my own methodologies for
writing sales copy over the years that I
want to pass on to you if I can impart
these to you you can get the same
results that I have and that my clients
have as well but I'm going to challenge
you with this as I start teaching this
as I start sharing these techniques with
you you may be
tempted to disassociate to check out to
get distracted to look at your phone to
scroll social media you might think that
what I'm talking about isn't relevant to
you or it may even challenge beliefs
about what you think is okay ethical and
even moral Integrity when it comes to
writing sales copy and if that bothers
you I would recommend that you don't
watch the rest of this video but I think
if you can listen to strateg IES that
work which by the way I'm going to tell
you this I believe the way that I have
modified a lot of the system has the
highest level of Integrity the highest
level of Ethics the highest level of
morals but when I I've worked with
thousands of people over the years I
found that not everybody feels
comfortable especially when people come
into my coaching program where I coach
people every single week on how to
create sales copy advertising campaigns
that's exactly what I do over at my
website Jeremiah Kowski
docomond growth accelerator program you
can find the waiting list over here at
Jeremiah kowsky do.com as I work with
you through establishing and
implementing these strategies what
you're going to find here on YouTube If
you subscribe to this channel if you
follow what I'm doing you're going to
find where I'm going to be giving you
one or two of the key strategies that
have gotten my clients the most success
absolutely free here and so what this is
this video it's basically going to be a
master class for you that you can go
through that you can watch and I would
recommend many of you you're going to
repeatedly watch this video you're going
to turn it on maybe even once or twice a
week when you're in the middle of
writing your sales copy you're going to
bookmark this video and save it to be
able to do that okay so I want to dive
right into the methodology that I use
for writing sales copy and the best way
that I do to write sales copy is it
always starts with a
shower you might be like what the heck
are you talking about it's starts with
going through a routine brushing my
teeth making my bed maybe picking up a
few things around my house taking a
shower and can I tell you this that I
used to be resistant to doing this and
this is one of those things that if you
can spend maybe 20 30 minutes in a
routine before you go into writing sales
copy of picking up a few things around
your house stuff like that it will start
to organize your ideas and so here's
what I recommend is to spend that time
simultaneously setting your
intention for what you are going to
write sales copy about okay so while I'm
doing the dishes while I might be
picking up my kitchen cleaning up my
office while I might be brushing my
teeth taking a shower maybe scrubbing a
toilet or two something like that for
about 20 to 30 minutes I'm going to be
thinking intentionally about the outcome
that I want from the sales copy I get a
vision in my mind for who I'm writing
the sales copy for and what I want to
project and portray okay and so when
you're writing sales copy what it
actually is and this is why it's
different than any other form of writing
it's different than technical writing
it's different than writing a novel it's
different than writing emails or social
media content or descriptions of posts
sales copy is about energy
transfer okay
don't check out here this isn't woooo by
the way CU I'm going to prove this to
you in about 2 minutes words and
visuals have the ability to create
images inside of people's minds how many
of you have ever read a fiction novel
before right I got a couple of them here
over in my shelf we got
um
The Chronicles of Narnia right here okay
we have um oh what's another one right
here I
have piercing the darkness by Frank
petti right here this is a novel that's
written it's a it's a it's a it's it's a
crazy Journey that the author takes you
into the
experience with them okay and you might
see even behind me the video games that
I have and things like this and and and
again listen I'm going to I'm going to
say this don't check out
please you may be challenged to ignore
what I am about to say because it
doesn't sound like what everybody else
teaches okay I need you to pay attention
to this proper sales copy creates images
in the mind of the person that you are
writing the copy towards and the image
in their mind is
this the full entire experience that
they will feel emotionally after they
buy from
you I'm going to say that again your
sales copy is for one purpose and one
purpose only to impart vision and ideas
about in their
mind what they will
experience after they they purchase from
you but they have not bought anything
from you yet they're just imagining it
so correct sales copy stimulates the
imagination to the same level that a
bestselling novelist
will it stimulates the imagination the
same way that an expert film director
would but you what you are doing is you
are writing a film and a movie on the
mind
of those that you are writing sales copy
to and the
heart you are triggering the heart of
those who you write sales copy to can I
can I tell you this words have the power
to
trigger feelings
right if you think about a death in your
family that triggers sadness I don't
want you to go there mentally let's not
go there but what if I talk
about the powerful amazing things that
you can do when you write sales copy and
the ability to only have to work 5 to 10
hours a week and still be able to make
500,000 a million dollars in a business
or even heck $5,000 in a business
without burning yourself out and the
fact that listen most people are
programmed against this through
Corporate America
and that what you have to learn how to
do is you have to learn how to
rewire your habits and gain new skills
in order to do this which is exactly
what we help people do in my accelerator
program as well as on my YouTube channel
right here okay but I want to pause here
I'm going to pull back the curtain
again don't check out from what I'm
teaching don't turn off your brain don't
disassociate what I might be sharing
with you right now may trigger you to
disassociate and shut
down because it doesn't sound like what
everybody else is saying but it is what
works okay you have to learn to write
sales copy in a
way that triggers positive emotions and
one of the best ways that I use to start
writing sales copy
is I might do stuff around my house I
might go for a walk around my
neighborhood and I will start speaking
out of my mouth ideas for what I want to
sell I will start verbalizing these
things and then if I verbalize it and
and I really like it and I like what I
said and this is the powerful part about
it that I need you to pay attention to I
need you to understand
this because we all have things that do
this for us but often times in our
business it's nearly impossible for
people because of how they have been
wired by their life experiences okay
this is not a mindset or a woow woo
strategy this is practical and this is
exactly what the best copywriters in
history have been able to
do sales copywriting is about triggering
emotions in people that ALS Al get
validated by Logic so you end up
triggering and firing in the brain both
the emotional centers and The Logical
centers at the same
time to where what it does is it
convinces the brain of the person that
you're writing sales copy to your Target
customer that what is written in the
copy is both
factual as well as it will work for them
and it feels really good and it excites
the
senses to where it becomes
irresistible to them to do something to
take action okay so again Focus
here you have to learn how to
communicate in a way that is
irresistible to your target client
you have to learn how to communicate in
a way that is so enticing that is it is
mouthwatering it's like if I go out
there and I find an Apple that's a red
juicy apple and I bite into it and it
starts dripping the juices that come out
of it and it just tastes so sweet and
good how many of y'all want one of those
apples right now and then if I take that
apple and I start to create a crust and
I bake it into an apple pie we start
cooking that apple pie and it fills the
house with a smell of the apple pie and
we got a little bit of whipped cream and
some ice cream and we take that apple
pie listen some of y'all might hate
apple pie and you might be nauseated by
what I'm saying right now I apologize if
that's the case I can't speak for
everybody
okay but whatever whatever your flavor
is all right think about that whatever
your your favorite food is maybe you
enjoy eating a kale salad
with some pecans and some cranberries
and some chicken breast right okay I
think I think that tastes pretty good as
well I think it's amazing and you put
some nice raspberry vinegret dressing on
there and you bite into it and it just
lights up the senses a little bit of
pepper on top of there right maybe a
little bit of what you know some Salsa
Mexican food I love that right okay so
you're sales copy has to excite the
senses through written
word and most people have no clue how to
do that they have no idea how they don't
know how to use the words that they
write to create images in people's minds
that that let them feel certain
things but can I tell you this have you
ever read a novel or have you ever seen
a product in a TV commercial or have you
ever gone to a restaurant and seing on
the menu something that just excited
like you just felt something it just
pulled you and you had to have it
right this happens in dating by the way
you see a beautiful woman or or or or a
handsome man that you want to connect
with and then you end up talking with
them and literally the communication and
the conversation just excites you to no
end that you want to get to know them
deeper and you want to go in for a kiss
and we'll we'll end the conversation
there
right that is what good sales copy
does but it does it translated for what
you are selling to people okay so what
you have to do is you have to start to
understand what motivates people to take
action what are they moving away away
from moving away from Pain towards
pleasure and your sales copy needs to
get very
[Music]
very
specific
about the
dream
desire and dare I say it because it's a
bit of a controversial word
right
here the
fantasy that they fantasize about in
their mind of what they wish reality was
that they're not experiencing right now
okay so you have to learn how to write
specifically words that tap into the
dreams and desires they have that create
a vision a Fantastical fantasy Vision
that they will say I have to have that I
must have it when you're reading a book
this this book is actually identified as
a fantasy novel okay so this is a great
example of this I think The Chronicles
of Narnia is a great example of this
because it is both fantasy and yet it
is by most
considerations G-rated content it's not
anything that you wouldn't want your
kids reading um it's it shows the
battles between good and evil it says
right here in a world of Fantastical
creatures
okay and so this is a fantasy that
creates a fantasy world in the Mind
through written words
so effective sales copy does the same
thing that a book like that would
do that a book like this would do this
would be considered more of a spiritual
quasi scientific uh uh science fiction
fantasy right here I have a novel series
that I'm reading right now called the
three body problem and the second book
is called the Dark Forest right here
this is a
Fantastical uh uh science fiction
universe that it invites you into
creates a vision in your mind of what
those things are okay what does do a
video game
do I have a couple of my favorite
fantasy video game uh books right here
we have the Legend of Zelda right here
takes you into an immersive
world where you get to fight Fantastical
creatures and you get to be the hero in
these Adventures you get to go right
into a portal into a world that most
people may have never experienced before
and I've been playing the Zelda game
since I was younger the Nintendo 64
right here my friends I even have
literally the first Zelda game right
here this is the first one that ever
came out for the old uh Nintendo systems
it's a f it's a fantasy world that you
can dive into and go on an adventure
on some of you might be shutting down
right now as I'm sharing this here's
another one it's called Skyrim right
here it's a it's a it's another
incredible world that you can go into in
a video
game don't shut down with what I'm
talking about here okay because this has
everything to do with you writing
effective sales copy is that when you
can
learn how to tell a
story in a way that triggers the mind of
a
buyer to get them to take action that is
specific it Taps into their dream
desires and fantasy
and you write those words
down your sales copy
becomes a thousand times more effective
than your closest competitor now here's
the thing this is why I don't like using
AI for this I like using AI to
brainstorm I think chat GPT and and I
actually have been using Google Gemini
advance I found Google Gemini advanc as
of the time of this recording is
actually one of the better AIS for doing
this it helps trigger my own brain with
ideas that I could write in sales copy
but here's the number one way that I
actually use to write sales
copy that is effective and I have a
method that I actually walk through
remember I mentioned that I will start
cleaning up my house picking up my house
doing all this the next stage that I
have is I enter into my own Fantastical
world
and I do this some of you might be
wondering why I have a science fiction
novel here where I have video games I
might read a chapter of this book for 5
to 10 minutes this is literally listen
don't check out here don't ignore what
I'm about to say pay attention to what
I'm about to say for most every aspect
of business I would not give you this
advice
discipline to not distract yourself and
be entertained and check out your brain
is important to both your reputation in
business as well as the ability to make
money in business and I that is an
irrefutable
fact but there is something
else that I believe is why most business
owners struggle to write sales copy and
it's a secret of every good sales copy
copywriter that I have ever
met is they have some sort of fictional
Fantastical entertainment experience
that they tap into so what I do is I
will start with the
discipline cleaning up my house
organizing things brushing my teeth
making my bed and then just like I did
when I was a kid now that I did all my
chores quote unquote I go out there and
I play a little bit for about 10 minutes
15 minutes not a lot of time by the way
10 to 15 minutes is not enough time to
completely distract you from the things
that you need to do but I can tell you
this is that the very best sales copy
ideas that I ever gotten have come out
of these experiences when I might be
reading a novel or playing a video game
for about 5 to 10 maybe 15 minutes I
might watch
an episode of a TV show on Netflix with
the
intention of actually removing my focus
that I just spent the last 30 minutes
doing okay so let let me map this out
for you let me draw this out for you so
this makes
sense I'm going to start with
[Music]
20 to 30 minutes of chores stuff okay
then I'm going to go
to 10 to 15 minutes of
entertainment mindless
entertainment 10 to 15
minutes now in this I set my
intention for the sales copy that I want
to write okay the 20 to 30 minutes I
start thinking about the Prospect and
what I want to accomplish and the things
like that during this
time I
disconnect and I really Zone in and
focus and I learn to let go of all the
thoughts that are going through my head
because what ends up happening is is
often times we end up focusing way too
hard and you can also learn meditation
exercises to do this I find that
entertainment actually can work faster
than a meditation so what I do is I
learn to to Zone in on the virtual world
that I might be reading about in a book
I might Zone in on the virtual world
that I'm playing in a video game I might
even play a sports video game last night
I I played a a hockey video game that I
love we got we got this uh Sega Genesis
NHL 94 right here 1994 this is a game
that I played for years when I was
younger and it and it gets me right back
into that childlike about 6 to 8 10
years old state of mind and so this is
something that I encourage people to do
what are some of the things that you can
do during this time right here I want
you to think back to when you were
between the ages of about 6 to 12 years
old right before a lot of the hormones
with puberty took over literally what
were the things that you did for fun
after you did your chores or school work
during that time do those things I will
literally play the same video games I
played at that
time like like the exact games that I
played when I was younger because it
gets me into a state of mind where I
don't have worries where I don't have
these fears and I don't have the bills
hanging over me but I only do it for
about 10 to 15 minutes that's about how
long it takes otherwise we really start
disassociating and then that becomes
toxic and that becomes dangerous and
that becomes what we want to be careful
of so now what I'll do is when I notice
that I'm fully zoned in on the game this
is what I've disciplined myself to do is
I turn the game
off and I open up my computer and
generally what I've liked to do recently
is I'll open up
YouTube and I'll open up
Facebook not for the intention of
scrolling mindlessly on those platforms
by the way scrolling social media could
be another thing that you can do for
this you could scroll social media for
10 to 15 minutes sometimes I do that as
well but what you're looking for is you
want to
find similar content on
YouTube to what you are about to sell to
people as well as similar offers on
Facebook that you want to sell to people
so what I will do is I will start
scrolling through
YouTube and social media and Facebook
and I will find content that is similar
to what I want to share with people that
I want to show to people that I want to
express to people okay so like if I go
over to YouTube right here on my
computer you can see I was actually
writing some sales copy for a client
yesterday and I pulled
up they were doing a live event that was
a music event and I actually pulled up
some live music events while I was
writing sales copy and then I went over
to Tony Robbins and I started watching
Tony Robbins latest uh training that he
literally just did last week I had this
playing in the background while I was
writing the sales copy it got me into
the state of mind I had it muted by the
way I wasn't listening to the content I
was just watching
it and it got me into the state of mind
and the thinking and the thought process
that I wanted to get into that could get
me aligned right
with what was going to have the best
sales copy come out of me okay and so
what I'm doing is I'm not necessarily
disassociating with that so the third
stage is I'll go over
to
YouTube and generally I like using
Facebook Facebook and YouTube I find are
the two best for doing this as I'll go
to YouTube and I'll watch some content
on a certain topic and then I'll go over
to
Facebook and I'll start looking at which
advertising campaigns are being
advertised to me which products are
being advertised to me are they
competitors we'll start clicking on
certain landing pages and
offers
okay and what I do is I end up copying
all of the sales copy from various
landing pages and offers that I find I
have no clue who this is I literally
just clicked the first ad that I saw
clicked on
it okay let's scroll down let's go find
another one here's another landing page
and I'll copy these
over some different advertising
campaigns to give me ideas for a sales
copy to create what is called a swipe
file
okay so again this is my process for
writing exceptional sales copy as I will
create a swipe file by pulling ideas
from other people that are teaching
similar content to me I might even take
a YouTube video that they created that
is very similar to what I want to sell
and then I can find the pieces of it and
bring that into the artificial
intelligence and then I will start to
brainstorm with the AI on what the pain
points are of the prospect what are they
struggling with I'll have it generate
the Epiphany bridge and this is where we
go into the part of the ultimate
salesletter book by Dan Kennedy that he
talks about that you really really want
to understand about who you are selling
to is you want to dive deeper into the
negative experiences of the people that
you are selling to okay if I'm going way
too fast through this let's just back up
here and recap what I just shared okay
I'll start with the intention of what I
want to create a sales letter with
chores 10 10 to 15 minutes of
disconnection and entertainment okay
disconnects the mind I might even throw
in a 5 minute meditation at the end of
this that's optional recently I've
stopped doing that don't need to then
I'll go to YouTube and Facebook and I'll
start finding whether it be Facebook
groups I'll start finding YouTubers that
have a similar vibe that I'm trying to
get out there they make me feel the way
that I want to on YouTube that I'm
expressing so so I might find some of my
even top competitors or people that I
might strive to be like I'll literally
watch Dan Kennedy uh Russell Brunson
I'll watch Alex Hermos I'll watch uh uh
I love love her how many of y'all know
who uh Jasmine star is as well Jasmine
star is just incredible when it comes to
her content that she teaches I yesterday
I was struggling to write sales copy and
and and I hope one day uh I know some
people that that I have mutual friends
with her I watched this video and I
watched about half of it and it
literally inspired me seeing her
confidence throughout the Journey of of
of launching her sales copy right here I
wasn't even necessarily paying attention
to what she was
saying I was just listening to her
energy and the Cadence and the
confidence and the tone that she was
talking about the confidence in what she
I mean look at she's she is just an icon
of confidence so you can't deny that
right you know I I told my wife the
other day I was like I I want to be like
Jasmine star when I grow up but you know
in a in Jeremiah Kowski level of
confidence I obviously you know don't
don't don't look like her but if that
makes sense but what that was was I was
able to borrow from the
energy of other mentors that are
successful
influencers millionaire mentor mentors
hundred million mentors that are out
there to get a Vibe for their energy
over here and then I go over to
Facebook because I advertise on Facebook
I want you to think about where are you
advertising where are you marketing
where do your prospects exist where do
they live okay and so for me that's
Facebook and I will start scrolling
through the news feed looking for cont
content that is relevant to what I am
trying to sell let's say I'm trying to
sell people on how to create exceptional
ads and write ads copy I'm going to
click on ads from people that are
selling other classes related to ads
okay and you might be thinking Jeremiah
so what you're doing is you're just
copying other people you just don't have
enough original ideas yourself that you
just got to Jack other people's ideas no
not at all what I'm doing is I am
stimulating and triggering my own mind
after going through this exercise
because what I've done is I've set my
intention while doing some hard
things then I entertain myself over here
to disconnect and then I go back to my
intention I get the energy off of the
YouTube videos that I watch and then I
scroll Facebook and I find offers from
different competitors that are out there
that might be marketing to me and let's
say I don't see their offers on social
media you want to know what I can do I
can go to their pages on social media
and I can find what they are advertising
so let's say that I might look at let's
say Jasmine star for instance right here
let's just let's just use her an example
because she's she's really incredible
and she's got a lot of great different
offers and stuff that she's doing I
don't even know if she's marketing
anything but you can go to any page on
social media and click on page
transparency and see which ads they are
running by going to the ad Library so
while she's not running any ads right
now I can see the previous ads that she
was running okay so I can see these are
ads that Jasmine was running I can click
on them and I can start to find sales
letters and sales copy that is in the
same vibe that I was watching over here
okay I might go over and find a sales
letter
from Dan Kennedy right here let's click
on let's click on Dan Kennedy let's type
this
in magnetic
marketing
okay let's go to Magnetic marketing
right here let's see if they're running
ads to this Russell Brunson purchased
this they are running ads let's see
which ads magnetic marketing is running
okay I can go to the ads library and I
can find which ads they are running
direct response marketing and sales
copyrighting ads we're going to click on
an ad and we're going to see the landing
page that they're sending people to so
you can literally swipe and create a
swipe file of the very best headlines
and sales copy from some of the best
marketers and see what their landing
pages look like and their structure by
going to the ads
library and finding the sales copy and
finding the language and the structure
of how the landing page is structured
and
written okay so then what I'll do is I
will copy not the not necessarily the
whole landing page but sometimes I will
I'll copy the whole landing page from
multiple different competitors and stuff
like that and then I will start reading
through the sales copy I'll start
finding what are headlines that draw me
in that are relevant to what I might be
sharing with my prospects that I might
be teaching and then I bring that into
artificial intelligence and I start
brainstorming and asking it questions
about the the mentality of the prospect
from
here what keeps them awake at night the
prospect that I'm trying to sell to the
people that these other sales letters
are written
towards I will borrow from those ideas
okay what are they afraid of what are
they angry about what are their top
three daily frustrations what trends are
occurring in their life what do they
secretly and ardently desire what is
their built-in bias do they have their
own language are they selling something
similar what have they tried before and
failed and when you can start to
understand this you start to get into
the
mind of your target Prospect so what I
am doing is I am bringing all of this
together I bring my swipe
file and I open up the number one sales
copyrighting tool that I have is either
I'll open up Apple notes on my
computer or I'll open
up a Google go doc and this is where
every sales letter starts and I will
just start writing the ideas that come
to mind about how I would express my
business to people about how I would
write headlines I might be asking chat
GPT to write me certain Headlines by the
way one of my favorite prompts of chat
GPT is write a headline in the tone of
Dan Kennedy Sandy Kowski which is my mom
who is a expert copywriter for years who
was also mentored by Dan
Kennedy and Russell Brenson and bring
all of those together to create a sales
letter to write headlines to create a
storytelling aspect to generate what are
the pain points what is the struggle
what is the unique selling proposition
to create attention interest desire
action sales copy called Ada to create
Pas sales copy problem agitate solution
we want to agitate the problem that the
prospect is having and point to the fact
that we have a solution and all of this
wrapped up and brought
together creates words that transfer a
vision of who you are it builds trust
with the prospect what they will
experience after they buy from you and
it will lead them
mentally along a journey in their mind
that the only logical best decision to
make is to make a purchase with
you and that's that's what you need to
learn how to do is you need to learn how
to communicate in a way that excites
people that draws them into that but you
will only understand that when you
understand what their pain is what
they're struggling with what they're
trying to run away from the overwhelm
the fear the worry and how many of y'all
after I've mentioned this you're
watching this you're like Jeremiah I
feel overwhelmed by doing this process
that's what I hear from a lot of people
because they've never done this before
this is why I say to break down just
start with before you write sales copy
go do something fun get into a playful
State of Mind start watching some
YouTube videos start looking at other
sales letters and create a swipe file
start signing up on email lists for
other people that are other marketers in
your industry and start seeing which
emails that they're sending to you did
you know that some of the best offers in
sales copy are not ran in ads but
they're in follow-up emails after you
sign up for the ad meaning
I might find a landing page right here
for an event that I can sign up for with
my email address but the follow-up email
that they send me two weeks later
actually has some of the best sales copy
that I might be able to borrow from for
my offer or my industry we have to get
past this
need to have to reinvent the wheel you
don't need to reinvent the wheel there
is enough people and marketers and
people out there that have spent
hundreds of millions of dollars in sales
copyrighting and and and marketers and
advertising to create these campaigns
that you can borrow those
ideas not to copy but to stimulate your
mind for your own ideas and when you can
learn how to do this when you can learn
how to stimulate your mind to to write a
story and you want to write a story just
like these other sales letters that
we're finding every sales letter has a
story 21 Elite marketers share direct
response strategy that produced the
biggest bang for their
Buck you've tried all this is this is
storytelling this is telling a story of
what the prospect
wants right here this is a story of what
they will experience on the other side
of signing up for this offer so when you
can learn to tell the story that creates
a vision and you can also use photos and
visuals and video to do this as well and
you bring all of this in a way that
excites the senses of the prospect they
will find it nearly impossible to say no
to whatever it is that you have to
offer now this is not something that
generally people learn overnight it
takes time and one of the best ways to
learn this is to have somebody that has
been doing it a while work with you to
show you exactly what that is and that's
exactly what we do in my client growth
accelerator program as I work with my my
clients every week on their sales copy
to write it I help rewrite it we do ad
copy hot seats we do sales page hot
seats we work with you through
critiquing and looking at your sales
copy you can literally any day of the
week post it inside of our community and
have us give feedback with where your
copy is because it's the number one
thing that influences if your sales are
going to grow and I think that that's
where one of the truest values is is
having the support as well as the
accountability you know listen going
along this process you will find that
you're going to want to get distracted
people want to give up it's going to get
hard things might not always go how you
want them to when you have somebody like
myself in your corner working with you
every single week to tweak
things you're not going to get it the
first time that's okay okay you're not
supposed to not everybody
does it's better to actually go about
this in a relaxed manner in a manner
that feels really good that's peaceful
and one of the biggest things that I
love to impart in my clients they always
say is Clarity breakthrough and inner
peace about the actions that they're
taking not just a false sense of Peace
but true peace because they know that
they know that they know that when they
work with me they get the best results
and so again I would encourage you if
you're watching this video still join
the waiting list for my client growth
accelerator that when we do open the
doors to this the next time we do at the
time of this recording it's about $200 a
month to be in there for $200 a month it
can generate you
$200,000 a month or $2,000 a month or
$20,000 a month like a lot of the
clients that we worked with whichever
level of income that you want to make I
can help get you there and I'd love to
work with you to get the clarity and the
focus and dial in your message in your
sales copy to start to make things work
with you so that you're not struggling
on your own that you get to have me a
part of your team so that I get to join
your team and work with you and be a
part of your long-term success strategy
I'd love to be a part of that with you
jump on the waiting list for the
accelerator and listen if this video has
helped you share it with somebody and
let me know in the comments what is well
you would like to see some future videos
from Me Maybe This has inspired some
ideas with you maybe you got some
concerns maybe you got some worries
maybe you got some stuff that you're not
quite sure about that I've shared here
today leave in the comments below and
I'd love to answer those with you and
maybe make another video that unpacks
those ideas with you what I just shared
with you today I believe will help you
create the best sales copy and get
started on your journey by the way I
have a free gift as well I didn't
mention it at the at the beginning of
the
video because I'm glad that you got to
the end here if you actually go over to
my website over at Jeremiah Kowski decom
I have a link at least at the time of
this
recording free chat GPT prompt download
it's at Jeremiah Kowski
docomo like 5 years from now in chat GPT
is not a thing you know whatever the the
latest thing is you'll find it on my
website you can sign up and it's a
Google doc that you can get access to
and this Google doc has my number one
sales copy prompts that we have
developed that have generated eight
figures to write sales copy it has chat
GPT list out the pain points The
Epiphany Bridge right here how to find
what is the solutions that people are
looking for you can find the link as
well below in the description the
outcome generated it it'll walk you
through generating the outcome that
you're trying to impart to people these
are prompts that you can paste into chat
GPT to generate sales copy that will
work for you this will be a great
starting phase for you not to
necessarily create the copy that you're
going to put on your landing page it's
going to work so a lot of people are
becoming very Savvy to what's AI
generated and what's not but it will
inspire your own mind in the right
direction that's going to create the
best copy that converts and so go grab
that it's totally free it's over at my
website and I think it'll really help
you we've had thousands of people
download it and they've said it's it's
the best okay so listen thanks for
watching this love to see you in my
accelerator program here when we do open
the doors next when we open up the
waiting list
I'll see you on our next video we'll
talk soon